wondering about the status of your
health insurance claim with ICICI
Lombard your claim status is just a few
Taps away there are three simple ways to
check your cashless or reimbursement
claim status effortlessly
the first and the most convenient option
is to check your claim status through
our IL take care app
simply tap on claims
select the policy number
tap on track your claim
and choose your claim number the IL take
care app will then display your claim
status download the app now to check
your claim status another method to
check your claim status is through
WhatsApp via the number shown on screen
our responsive intelligent assistant
rear will assist you as You Follow the
guided flow to view the real-time status
of your claim
[Music]
you also have the option to view your
claim status on our website select
claims click on help claims from the
drop down menu enter your claim number
or policy details to view the status of
your claim
visit our website now
you may see one of these four statuses
while checking the progress of your
claim through either one of these
methods
[Music]
if your claim status is on the process
it means your claim is under assessment
your claim request will just take eight
days from the date of receipt of
complete documents
if the status of your claim shows
approved it means your claim has been
approved and your approved amount will
be paid within two days
if the status of your claim shows
queried it means you need to submit some
more information or documents simply
respond to the query and share the
missing documents and information
[Music]
[Applause]
if the claim is not in line with the
policy terms and conditions your claim
status shows rejected you may visit ril
take care app to check the reason for
rejection a letter detailing the reasons
will be sent to your registered email ID
with ICICI lumbar checking your claim
status is fast and convenient
[Music]